<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="dessert">Dessert</string>
    <string name="baking">Baking</string>
    <string name="salads">Salads</string>
    <string name="snack">Snack</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake">Chocolate Cake</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="cheesecake">Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="classic_chocolate_cake">Classic Chocolate Cake</string>
    <string name="homemade_bread">Homemade Bread</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="cucumber_and_tomato_salad">Cucumber and Tomato Salad</string>
    <string name="caesar_salad">Caesar Salad</string>
    <string name="chips">Chips</string>
    <string name="step7_chips">Step 7: Serve and Enjoy</string>
    <string name="info_chips">Once the potato chips have cooled, serve them as a delicious homemade snack or side dish. Feel free to enjoy them plain or with your favorite dip or sauce.</string>
    <string name="info_chips6">Remove the chips from the oven and immediately sprinkle them with salt while they are still hot. Let the chips cool on a wire rack to maintain their crispiness.</string>
    <string name="chips_step6">Step 6: Cool and Season</string>
    <string name="chips_step5">Step 5: Bake</string>
    <string name="chips_info_5">Place the baking sheets in the preheated oven and bake for about 15-20 minutes, or until the potato chips are golden brown and crispy. Keep an eye on them, as cooking times may vary depending on the thickness of your slices.</string>
    <string name="chips_info_4">Line one or more baking sheets with parchment paper or a silicone baking mat for easy cleanup. Arrange the seasoned potato slices in a single layer on the baking sheets. Make sure they are not overlapping to allow even cooking.</string>
    <string name="chips_step4">Step 4: Arrange on Baking Sheets</string>
    <string name="chips_step3">Step 3: Season the Chips</string>
    <string name="chips_step2">Step 2: Prepare the Potatoes</string>
    <string name="chips_step1">Step 1: Preheat the Oven</string>
    <string name="chips_info1">Preheat your oven to 400°F (200°C).</string>
    <string name="chips_info2">Scrub the potatoes thoroughly to remove dirt and debris. You can leave the skins on for added texture and flavor. Using a sharp knife or a mandoline slicer, slice the potatoes into very thin rounds. The thinner you slice them, the crispier your chips will be.</string>
    <string name="chips_info3">Place the potato slices in a large bowl. Drizzle them with olive oil and toss to coat evenly. You can also sprinkle your desired seasonings over the chips and toss to combine.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step1">Step 1: Make the Caesar Dressing</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step2">Step 2: Prepare the Croutons</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step3">Step 3: Assemble the Salad</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step4">Step 4: Add the Dressing</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step5">Step 5: Optional Additions</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_step6">Step 6: Serve and Enjoy</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info1">In a small bowl, whisk together the mayonnaise, 2 tablespoons of grated Parmesan cheese, lemon juice, Dijon mustard, minced garlic, Worcestershire sauce, salt, and black pepper. Taste and adjust the seasoning as needed.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info2">If you\'re making homemade croutons, cut bread into cubes, toss with olive oil, and bake in a preheated oven at 350°F (175°C) for about 10-15 minutes until they are golden brown and crisp.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info3">In a large salad bowl, place the torn Romaine lettuce leaves. Add the croutons and 1/2 cup of grated Parmesan cheese.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info4">Drizzle the Caesar dressing over the salad. Toss everything together until the lettuce leaves are evenly coated with the dressing.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info5">If you\'d like to add protein, consider grilling chicken breast or shrimp separately and adding them to the salad. For a traditional Caesar flavor, you can also add anchovy fillets, finely minced or mashed into the dressing.</string>
    <string name="ceaser_salat_info6">Serve your Caesar salad immediately, garnishing with extra grated Parmesan cheese if desired. Enjoy your classic Caesar salad as a side dish or add protein to make it a satisfying main course!</string>
    <string name="cucumber_step1">Step 1: Prepare the Vegetables</string>
    <string name="cucumber_step2">Step 2: Make the Dressing</string>
    <string name="cucumber_step3">Step 3: Assemble the Salad</string>
    <string name="cucumber_step4">Step 4: Add Optional Feta Cheese</string>
    <string name="cucumber_step5">Step 5: Season and Serve</string>
    <string name="cucumber_info1">Slice the cucumbers and place them in a large salad bowl. Slice or cut the tomatoes into wedges and add them to the bowl. Thinly slice the red onion and add it to the bowl as well. Tear the fresh basil leaves and chop the parsley. Add them to the bowl with the vegetables.</string>
    <string name="cucumber_info2">In a separate small bowl, whisk together the olive oil, red wine vinegar or balsamic vinegar, minced garlic, Dijon mustard, honey (if using), salt, and black pepper. Taste and adjust the seasoning as needed.</string>
    <string name="cucumber_info3">Pour the dressing over the vegetables in the salad bowl. Gently toss everything together until the vegetables are evenly coated with the dressing.</string>
    <string name="cucumber_info4">If desired, sprinkle crumbled feta cheese over the top of the salad.</string>
    <string name="cucumber_info5">Taste the salad and adjust the salt and black pepper to your liking. Serve your cucumber and tomato salad immediately, or refrigerate it for a refreshing side dish. Enjoy!.</string>
    <string name="homemade_step1">Step 1: Activate the Yeast (if needed)</string>
    <string name="homemade_step2">Step 2: Mix the Dough</string>
    <string name="homemade_step3">Step 3: Knead the Dough</string>
    <string name="homemade_step4">Step 4: First Rise</string>
    <string name="homemade_step5">Step 5: Shape the Loaf</string>
    <string name="homemade_step6">Step 6: Second Rise</string>
    <string name="homemade_step7">Step 7: Preheat the Oven</string>
    <string name="homemade_step8">Step 8: Bake the Bread</string>
    <string name="homemade_step9">Step 9: Cool and Serve</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo1">If you\'re using regular active dry yeast (not instant yeast), you can activate it to ensure it\'s active. In a small bowl, combine the yeast, warm water, and sugar. Let it sit for about 5-10 minutes until it becomes frothy. If it doesn\'t froth, the yeast may be expired, and you should get a fresh packet.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo2">In a large mixing bowl, combine the flour and salt. If you activated the yeast in Step 1, add the yeast mixture to the bowl. If you\'re using instant yeast, you can add it directly to the flour. Mix everything together until a shaggy dough forms.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo3">Turn the dough out onto a floured surface. Knead the dough for about 8-10 minutes until it becomes smooth and elastic. You can also use a stand mixer with a dough hook attachment for this step.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo4">Place the kneaded dough in a greased bowl, cover it with a clean kitchen towel, and let it rise in a warm, draft-free place for about 1-2 hours, or until it has doubled in size.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo5">Once the dough has risen, punch it down to release any air bubbles. Shape the dough into a loaf by folding the edges towards the center and rolling it up tightly. Place the shaped dough into a greased or parchment-lined loaf pan.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo6">Cover the loaf pan with the kitchen towel and let it rise for an additional 30-45 minutes, or until it has risen slightly above the edge of the pan.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo7">Preheat your oven to 375°F (190°C).</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo8">If desired, brush the top of the loaf with oil for a softer crust. Bake the bread in the preheated oven for about 25-30 minutes, or until the top is golden brown and the bread sounds hollow when tapped on the bottom.</string>
    <string name="homemade_sinfo9">Remove the bread from the pan and let it cool on a wire rack for at least 30 minutes before slicing. Serve your homemade bread and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step1">Step 1: Preheat the Oven</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step2">Step 2: Prepare the Cake Batter</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step3">Step 3: Bake the Cake</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step4">Step 4: Prepare the Chocolate Frosting</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step5">Step 5: Frost the Cake</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_step6">Step 6: Serve and Enjoy</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info1">Preheat your oven to 350°F (175°C). Grease and flour two 9-inch (23 cm) round cake pans.</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info2">In a large mixing bowl, sift together the flour, sugar, cocoa powder, baking powder, baking soda, and salt. Add the eggs, buttermilk, vegetable oil, and vanilla extract to the dry ingredients. Mix until well combined. Gradually stir in the boiling water. The batter will be thin, but that\'s okay.</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info3">Pour the batter evenly into the prepared cake pans. Bake in the preheated oven for 30 to 35 minutes or until a toothpick inserted into the center comes out clean. Remove the cakes from the oven and allow them to cool in the pans for about 10 minutes. Then, transfer the cakes to a wire rack to cool completely.</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info4">In a large mixing bowl, beat the softened butter until creamy. Sift in the powdered sugar and cocoa powder, and beat until well combined. Add the milk and vanilla extract, and continue to beat until the frosting is smooth and fluffy.</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info5">Once the cakes have cooled completely, spread a layer of chocolate frosting on top of one of the cakes. Place the second cake on top and frost the top and sides of the entire cake.</string>
    <string name="classk_chocolate_info6">Slice and serve your classic chocolate cake. It\'s delicious on its own or with a scoop of ice cream! Enjoy your homemade classic chocolate cake!</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step1">Step 1: Preheat the Oven</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step2">Step 2: Prepare the Crust</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step3">Step 3: Make the Filling</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step4">Step 4: Bake the Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step5">Step 5: Cool and Refrigerate</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_step6">Step 6: Serve</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info1">Preheat your oven to 325°F (160°C).</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info2">In a bowl, combine the graham cracker crumbs, 1/4 cup of granulated sugar, and melted butter Press this mixture firmly into the bottom of a 9-inch (23 cm) springform pan to create the crust.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info3">In a large mixing bowl, beat the softened cream cheese until smooth and creamy, Add 1 1/4 cups of granulated sugar and vanilla extract to the cream cheese, and beat until well combined, Add the eggs, one at a time, mixing just until each egg is incorporated. Be careful not to overmix.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info4">Pour the cream cheese filling over the crust in the springform pan,  Tap the pan on the counter a few times to remove any air bubbles, Bake in the preheated oven for about 45-50 minutes, or until the edges are set but the center still jiggles slightly.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info5">Remove the cheesecake from the oven and let it cool in the pan on a wire rack for about 10 minutes, Then, run a knife around the edge of the pan to loosen the cheesecake from the sides, Allow the cheesecake to cool completely, then refrigerate it for several hours or overnight to set.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_info6">Serve your delicious cheesecake plain or with your favorite toppings, such as fruit compote, chocolate sauce, or whipped cream. Enjoy your homemade cheesecake!</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step1">Step 1: Prepare the Ingredients</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step2">Step 2: Prepare the Baking Pan</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step3">Step 3: Make the Cake Batter</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step4">Step 4: Bake the Cake</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step5">Step 5: Prepare the Frosting</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step6">Step 6: Frost the Cake</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_step7">Step 7: Serve and Enjoy</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info1">Gather all the necessary ingredients as listed in the recipe.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info2">Grease the baking pan with butter and dust it with flour or use parchment paper to prevent sticking.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info3">In one bowl, combine 220g of flour, 65g of cocoa powder, 7.5g of baking powder, 7.5g of baking soda, and a pinch of salt. In another bowl, beat 2 eggs and 350g of sugar until fluffy. Gradually add 240ml of milk, 120ml of vegetable oil, and 2 teaspoons of vanilla extract to the egg-sugar mixture, mixing well. Stir in 240ml of boiling water until the batter is smooth; it will be thin, which is normal.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info4">Pour the batter into the prepared baking pan. Place the pan in a preheated oven at 180°C (350°F). Bake the cake for approximately 30-35 minutes or until a wooden toothpick or knife inserted into the center comes out clean. Remove the cake from the oven and allow it to cool in the pan for a few minutes before transferring it to a cooling rack for complete cooling.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info5">In a small saucepan, heat 225g of butter until melted. Add 250g of powdered sugar and 85g of cocoa powder gradually, pouring in 120ml of milk while stirring. Cook the frosting, stirring until it thickens and becomes smooth. Remove it from the heat and add 2 teaspoons of vanilla extract.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info6">Pour the chocolate frosting over the cooled cake, spreading it evenly.</string>
    <string name="chocolatecake_info7">Let the cake cool completely and the frosting set before slicing and serving. Enjoy your homemade chocolate cake!</string>
    <string name="sugar">Sugar</string>
    <string name="flour">Flour</string>
    <string name="cocoa">Cocoa</string>
    <string name="baking_powder">Baking powder</string>
    <string name="salt">Salt</string>
    <string name="eggs">Eggs</string>
    <string name="milk">Milk</string>
    <string name="olive">olive</string>
    <string name="butter">Butter</string>
    <string name="smetana">Smetana</string>
    <string name="cream">Cream</string>
    <string name="soda">Soda</string>
    <string name="cucumber">Cucumber</string>
    <string name="tomatoes">Tomatoes</string>
    <string name="garlic">Garlic</string>
    <string name="potatoes">Potatoes</string>
</resources>